Priyata Mallick

SAP TECHNICAL CONSULTANT

Ph. 91051814150 | Email - priyatamallick.official@gmail.com

Overview

A strong team player with 3.2 years of experience with ability to create and deliver solutions. Dedicated to deliver development objectives within time with high quality code by maintaining all SAP and Project specific guideline. Diligent and focused to deliver objects on SAP ABAP on HANA, offering skills in RICEFW and OOPS ABAP.

Experience

Capgemini, Kolkata | Senior Analyst

04/2023 - Present

- Learnt client specific implementation process to fulfil requirements.
- · Developed enhancements for client specific needs, using enhancements and BADI.
- Offered accurate and efficient solutions and worked on Reports, IDOCs and Adobe form.
- Developed high quality code while implementing latest SAP techniques and guidelines.
- Documented and maintained technical specifications for the applications developed.
- Learn and develop Unix Scripts to move files from SAP to MQ.
- · Trained and mentored junior/new joiners to guide them through the project.

Capgemini, Kolkata | Analyst

02/2022 - 04/2023

- Shadowed senior team members to understand real time project requirements.
- · Learn to analyze the requirement individually and develop the logic accordingly.
- Worked on real time objects that enhance the knowledge to work on Proxy, Reports, and enhancements.
- Worked with SAP landscape and management of transport requests.
- Learn new syntaxes and implemented in the developments.

Capgemini, Kolkata | Analyst (as a Trainee)

08/2021 - 02/2022

- Attended courses to build understanding of industry specific processes in SAP ABAP.
- Learned basic ABAP concepts, fundamental to all SAP modules.
- Worked on assignments and case studies implementing ABAP concepts like OOALV, Adobe forms and RICEFW.

Education

Bachelor of Technology – Applied Electronics and Instrumentation– 9.03 DGPA

2021

Academy of Technology, Hooghly

Naihati Katyayani Girls' High School

Skills & abilities

- SAP S/4 for HANA
- ABAP OOPS
- Reports, DDIC, Function Modules, Enhancements, Proxy, IDOC, Adobe Forms, OOALV
- Workflow, OData (Self Grooming In Progress)
- Octane
- Solman
- Unix Shell Scripting on Putty

Certification & Achievements

Received appreciation from client-side QA team for proposing well detailed logic as a part of OneSAP RICEFW factory.

Mallick, Priyata 9051814150 priyatamallick.official@gmail.com